<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Code, lies, and blargles.]]></title>
  <link href="http://blrgl.com/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://blrgl.com/"/>
  <updated>2013-10-20T20:41:37+01:00</updated>
  <id>http://blrgl.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Sam Salisbury]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Migrating to OS X&mdash;Review]]></title>
    <link href="http://blrgl.com/blog/2013/10/20/migrating-to-os-x-review/"/>
    <updated>2013-10-20T18:00:00+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://blrgl.com/blog/2013/10/20/migrating-to-os-x-review</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><em>This <a href="">Mac OS X 10.8 Mountain Lion review</a> is part 2 of a <a href="http://blrgl.com/blog/series#migrating-from-windows-to-mac">series on migrating from Windows to Mac</a>.</em></p>

<blockquote><p>About 6 months ago I (a .NET developer) took over maintenance of an iOS app. This meant I needed to use a Mac, for the first time in 20 years. In order to avoid maintaining 2 separate workstations, I also switched to using OS X as my primary operating system, with Windows in a VM to continue my .NET work. Here&rsquo;s my take on making the switch&hellip;</p></blockquote>

<p>The transition from Microsoft Windows 8 to Mac OS X was not as clear-cut advantageous as the <a href="http://blrgl.com/blog/2013/10/18/migrating-to-macbook-review">transition from Dell to Apple hardware</a> was. There are some quite strange things for a Windows user to get used to in OS X. However, 6 months into this experiment, and I really don&rsquo;t think I&rsquo;ll ever go back to a pure Windows environment.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>Skip to:<br />
<strong><a href="#os-x-confusion">The Bad</a></strong>
 (<a href="#os-x-quitting">quitting</a>
| <a href="#os-x-fullscreen">fullscreen</a>
| <a href="#os-x-maximising">maximising</a>
| <a href="#os-x-snapping">snapping</a>) <br />
<strong><a href="#os-x-good">The Good</a></strong>
 (<a href="#os-x-navigation">Mission Control, Exposé and Spaces</a>
| <a href="#os-x-gestures">Gestures</a>
| <a href="#os-x-terminal">Terminal</a>) <br />
<strong><a href="#os-x-conclusion">The Conclusion</a></strong></p>

<h2><i class="icon-apple"></i> <a id="os-x"></a> The Operating System</h2>

<p><strong>Mac OS X (10.8) Mountain Lion</strong> running on a 15&ndash;inch MacBook Pro with Retina Display, 16GB RAM/512GB SSD/2.7GHz Core i7</p>

<p><a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/OS_X_Mountain_Lion">OS X Mountain Lion</a> is the first Mac OS I&rsquo;ve ever used in a work context, and the only one I&rsquo;ve used as an adult. Prior to this my only real experience of using a Mac was at school, as an 8 or 9 year old, putting together school newspapers using <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/System_7">System 7</a> machines. An experience I barely remember now&hellip;</p>

<p>My very first impressions of this operating system were not all favourable, although it was immediately more visually pleasing than Windows 8. Some of the odd skeuomorphism in the built-in apps was a little jarring, and window management left something to be desired. However, some features were really well implemented&hellip;</p>

<h2><i class="icon-remove"></i> <a id="os-x-confusion"></a> The Bad</h2>

<p>It might be unfair to classify all of the below as objective failures in OS X, some may be more to do with me having 20 years of Windows usage ingrained into my psyche. However, from my perspective the OS could be improved in these areas. So, here is a treatment of my initial frustrations transitioning to OS X. I&rsquo;ve highlighted a few key points that might be useful things to remember for anyone else undertaking the same journey.</p>

<h3><i class="icon-remove-circle"></i> <a id="os-x-quitting"></a> Closing Windows Does Not Terminate Applications</h3>

<p>Conversely, in Windows, you usually expect that closing a program&rsquo;s main window will end the program&rsquo;s main <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Process_(computing)">process</a>. If not, you can always look in the system tray (in fact, the &lsquo;<a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Taskbar#Taskbar_elements">notification area</a>&rsquo;) to verify whether the program is really dead or not. In OS X, only certain programs seem to die when you close all their windows. This upset me for about an hour when I realised I had tens of applications running that I thought I&rsquo;d stopped. However, a simple <code>⌥⇥</code> (<code>Option+Tab</code>) shows all running applications. You can then <em>quit</em> each one using a simple <code>⌘Q</code> (<code>Command+Q</code>). Terminating an application in OS X is always known as &lsquo;quitting&rsquo; an application. To <em>quit</em> is to end a process. You can <em>close</em> windows, but you can only <em>quit</em> applications.</p>

<blockquote><p>Note: In OS X, terminating an application is <em>always</em> known as <em>quitting</em> that application. The same terminology applies to processes in general. To <em>quit</em> is to end the process entirely.</p></blockquote>

<h3><i class="icon-resize-full"></i> <a id="os-x-fullscreen"></a> Full-Screen Apps Only Use One Monitor</h3>

<p>This is a very weird decision on the part of Apple. Making an app full-screen will blank out all the other monitors, rendering them useless. In my usual three-monitor setup, this renders the &lsquo;full-screen&rsquo; option totally useless. This issue will be <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/OS_X_Mavericks">fixed in the upcoming OS X Mavericks</a> release.</p>

<h3><i class="icon-plus"></i> <a id="os-x-maximising"></a> Maximising Windows Is Inconsistent</h3>

<p>Depending on the program, clicking the green + icon in the top left of a window can variously make the window full-height, full-width and full-height, do nothing at all, or go full-height and some arbitrary width. This seems odd for an otherwise highly consistent user interface, and means I pretty much <em>never use the feature,</em> since I don&rsquo;t know what it&rsquo;s supposed to do. Isn&rsquo;t this one of those things that should be shaved off the design?</p>

<h3><i class="icon-puzzle-piece"></i> <a id="os-x-snapping"></a> There Is No Built-In Window Snapping</h3>

<p>One of <a href="http://windows.microsoft.com/en-GB/windows7/products/features/snap">my favourite features in Windows</a> has been the ability to drag a window to the top, left, or right of the monitor, and have that window either maximise, or snap to the left or right and resize to half the available width. This kind of feature is sadly missing from OS X Mountain Lion. However, there is a brilliant free app called <a href="http://blog.boastr.net/downloads-secondbar-bettertouchtool-2/">Better Touch Tool</a> which adds window snapping, plus loads of other useful features to window management in OS X.</p>

<h2><i class="icon-check"></i> <a id="os-x-good"></a> The Good</h2>

<p>Along with the strange, there are some incredibly well-designed features in OS X, some of which are so good, in fact, that they have permanently altered some of my workflows, and changed my fundamental expectations of an OS. Here are three of the my favourite features in OS X.</p>

<h3><i class="icon-desktop"></i> <a id="os-x-navigation"></a> Mission Control, Exposé, and Spaces</h3>

<p>Mission Control, Exposé, and Spaces (multiple desktops) are the central window and app navigation features in OS X Mountain Lion, and they&rsquo;re really well implemented. <em>Nuf&#8217; said.</em> But really, these three core navigation features are game changers to any multi-window workflow. You can swipe four fingers left or right, to access <a href="http://mattgemmell.com/2011/07/27/using-spaces-on-os-x-lion/">as many desktops (sometimes called &lsquo;Spaces&rsquo;)</a> as you need. This is an astonishingly useful feature, especially when you don&rsquo;t have an external monitor. The quickness of a four-finger-swipe-up, to see all open windows and desktops, known as <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mission_Control_(OS_X)">Mission Control</a>, is also hugely useful. There is also an under-used four-finger-swipe-down gesture to <a href="http://www.apple.com/uk/osx/what-is/gestures.html#gallery-gestures-expose">show all windows belonging to the current application</a>, known as &lsquo;App Exposé&rsquo;.</p>

<p>I am no longer horrified by the idea of working without <a href="http://www.codinghorror.com/blog/2004/06/multiple-monitors-and-productivity.html">multiple</a> <a href="http://www.codinghorror.com/blog/2010/04/three-monitors-for-every-user.html">external</a> <a href="http://www.codinghorror.com/blog/2008/03/does-more-than-one-monitor-improve-productivity.html">monitors</a>.</p>

<h3><i class="icon-hand-up"></i> <a id="os-x-gestures"></a> Usable Gestures</h3>

<p>In OS X, for the first time ever, I use gestures constantly to interact with my work. From the swiping between desktops, to scrolling, zooming, rotating, and the simplicity of &lsquo;two-finger-click&rsquo; to access &lsquo;right-click&rsquo; menus, gestures in OS X are implemented in a way that makes them the quickest and easiest way to accomplish many tasks. The large trackpad means you barely ever need to look down at your hands, and can focus on the screen whilst working.</p>

<h3><i class="icon-terminal"></i> <a id="os-x-terminal"></a> Terminal, the command-line of OS X</h3>

<p><a href="http://www.apple.com/osx/apps/all.html#terminal">Terminal</a> is a huge breath of fresh air coming from the <a href="http://stackoverflow.com/questions/473839/help-me-make-my-windows-cmd-exe-console-work-more-like-a-linux-terminal">neglected Windows command line</a>. For a start, it provides sane, line-aware text selection, allowing you to select text in the same order as it was printed to the output stream. This is unlike the Windows command line&rsquo;s bizarre treatment of text as a <em>table</em> of characters to be selected in a grid. It also has tabs, so you can easily have multiple sessions open at once in the same window.</p>

<p>As a developer, I spend <em>a lot</em> of time on the command line. Having one that works in a sane and useful way is a massive boon. I even use Terminal on OS X to do all my <a href="http://git-scm.com/">Git</a> work when developing inside my Windows VM, by mapping the virtual Windows hard drive to a mount point in OS X. (Parallels Desktop makes this really easy.)</p>

<blockquote><p>As a developer, I spend <em>a lot</em> of time on the command line. Having one that works in a sane and useful way is a massive boon.</p></blockquote>

<h2><i class="icon-thumbs-up"></i> <a id="os-x-conclusion"></a> The Conclusion</h2>

<p>OS X Mountain Lion is a far more accomplished developer OS than Windows 8, especially on a laptop. I can&rsquo;t compare it with previous version of OS X, since this is the first one I&rsquo;ve used, but, coming from Windows, it&rsquo;s pretty much all upside. Usable multiple desktop support, coupled with a sensible command line, are enough by themselves to make this OS the only rational choice for a developer workstation.</p>

<blockquote><p>OS X Mountain Lion is a far more accomplished developer OS than Windows 8, especially on a laptop.</p></blockquote>

<p>The few complaints with respect to window management in OS X are easily mitigated with some free software, notably <a href="http://blog.boastr.net/what-is-bettertouchtool/">Better Touch Tool</a>.</p>

<p><strong>My recommendation: If you&rsquo;re currently using Windows for all your development work, no matter whether you&rsquo;re a Microsoft .NET developer, or any other kind of developer, get a Mac with OS X Mountain Lion. If you need to use Windows for development work, get <a href="http://www.parallels.com/products/desktop/">Parallels Desktop</a>.</strong></p>

<p>Thanks for reading, I&rsquo;d love to hear any feedback in the comments below :)</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Migrating to MacBook&mdash;Review]]></title>
    <link href="http://blrgl.com/blog/2013/10/18/migrating-to-macbook-review/"/>
    <updated>2013-10-18T10:38:00+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://blrgl.com/blog/2013/10/18/migrating-to-macbook-review</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><em>This <a href="">MacBook Pro with Retina Display review</a> is part 1 of a <a href="http://blrgl.com/blog/series#migrating-from-windows-to-mac">series on migrating from Windows to Mac</a>.</em></p>

<blockquote><p>Six months ago, I was lucky enough to take over development of an iOS App. This meant I needed <a href="http://www.apple.com/macbook-pro/">a Mac</a>. <em>I was a die-hard .NET developer, using Dell/Windows machines almost exclusively for the past 20 years. In short, I had pretty much no idea what to expect.</em> I wasn&rsquo;t convinced this would be a good idea&hellip; How can a developer, <em>a Microsoft developer,</em> live with a strange keyboard, an unfamiliar OS, shiny skeuomorphic apps, and, did I mention, a strange keyboard?! <em>It wasn&rsquo;t half as bad as I expected&hellip;</em></p></blockquote>

<!-- more -->


<p>Skip to:
<a href="#hardware">Hardware</a>
| <a href="#keyboard">Keyboard</a>
| <a href="#trackpad">Trackpad</a>
| <a href="#display">Display</a>
| <a href="#ports">Ports</a>
| <a href="#performance">Performance</a>
| <a href="#usability">Usability</a>
| <a href="#conclusion">Conclusion</a></p>

<h2><a id="hardware"></a> <i class="icon-laptop"></i> The Hardware</h2>

<p><strong>15&ndash;inch MacBook Pro with Retina Display, 16GB RAM, 512GB SSD, 2.7GHz Core i7</strong></p>

<p>The first thing I noticed was that the hardware was incredibly precisely manufactured. I know this is gross repetition, but it&rsquo;s true, and it&rsquo;s striking&thinsp;&mdash;&thinsp;even my ridiculously expensive <a href="http://www.dell.com/us/business/p/precision-m6500/pd">Dell &lsquo;Precision&rsquo; workstation</a> was shipped with a misaligned, slightly twisted lid. The lid on this beast shut with a pleasing thud, perfectly aligned.</p>

<blockquote><p>It&rsquo;s pretty amazing how little space this powerful beast takes up.</p></blockquote>

<p>It&rsquo;s also thin, really really thin. This is basically a desktop replacement, it&rsquo;s probably the most powerful computer I&rsquo;d ever used, and also, somehow, the thinnest and lightest. Sure, it&rsquo;s no MacBook Air, but for the power in there, it&rsquo;s pretty amazing how little space this powerful beast takes up.</p>

<h3><a id="trackpad"></a> <i class="icon-hand-up"></i> The Trackpad</h3>

<p>The large, clickable trackpad, smooth and precise, didn&rsquo;t rattle around with gentle usage on the MacBook, like it did in most of the brand new Dell laptops in use around the office. In fact, it didn&rsquo;t budge a millimetre even with six months of prolonged heavy-handed abuse. Its texture was very smooth, meaning that with any dampness it became quite grippy, impinging on the usual smooth glide accross its surface. However, its size, responsiveness, and precision meant it was an absolute pleasure to use.</p>

<h3><a id="display"></a> <i class="icon-desktop"></i> The Display</h3>

<p>The high resolution display&mdash;&lsquo;Retina&rsquo; display in marketing lingo&mdash; was pretty stunning, and text appeared silky-smooth, and totally rounded. Not a pixel in sight. This, unfortunately, completely made a mockery of anything lower-resolution. Other monitors which had seemed perfectly fine up to this point began to look like cheap toys.</p>

<h3><a id="ports"></a> <i class="icon-headphones"></i> <i class="icon-hdd"></i> <i class="icon-gamepad"></i> <i class="icon-print"></i> <i class="icon-printer"></i> The Ports</h3>

<p>On a MacBook Pro with Retina Display, there are the following ports:</p>

<ul>
<li>MagSafe 2 power port</li>
<li>2x USB3 (one on either side)</li>
<li>2x Thunderbolt</li>
<li>HDMI</li>
<li>Headphones</li>
<li>SDXC slot</li>
</ul>


<p>The layout of the USB, Thunderbolt, HDMI, headphones and other ports seems, simply, correct. Lined up as near to the base of the screen as possible, rather than arbitrarily half way down the keyboard, cables tend to stay out of the way.</p>

<p>I use one of the Thunderbolt ports to power a monitor (through a <a href="http://store.apple.com/uk/product/MB570Z/B/mini-displayport-to-dvi-adapter?fnode=78">Thunderbolt to HDMI adapter</a>), and hook up another monitor to the HDMI slot. I typically plug in a USB to ethernet adapter if I&rsquo;m at my desk, and switch off wireless. I can&rsquo;t wait to get my hands on <a href="http://store.apple.com/uk/product/MC914B/B/apple-thunderbolt-display-27-inch">one of these</a>, so I&rsquo;ll only need to use a single Thunderbolt port for two monitors and ethernet, reducing clutter a lot.</p>

<h3><a id="keyboard"></a> <i class="icon-keyboard"></i> The Keyboard</h3>

<p>The flat, short-action keyboard keys, were one of the things that had always put me off Apple laptops. However, in reality they were reasonably pleasing to use, and nowhere near as flimsy as they looked. <em>Tick.</em> Some aspects of the keyboard design, though, are definitely questionable&mdash;for a Windows guy at least.</p>

<blockquote><p>Some aspects of the keyboard design are definitely questionable.</p></blockquote>

<p><strong>The power button <i class="icon-off"></i> is &lsquo;just another&rsquo; key,</strong> on the top right of the keyboard. Whilst this keeps things very uniform, accidentally hitting the off button whilst typing is a little unnerving&hellip; Even though you still have to confirm before the machine actually powers down.</p>

<p><strong>The key known as &lsquo;Option&rsquo; in all the docs is mysteriously labelled &lsquo;Alt&rsquo;</strong> on the physical keyboard. I believe this is only on the UK keyboards, but it&rsquo;s pretty darn confusing. The option symbol (⌥) is there, fortunately, but one gets a sneaking suspicion a certain level of obfuscation has been built in on purpose by Apple, perhaps to make it easy to <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Criticism_of_Apple_Inc.#Comparison_with_a_cult.2Freligion">identify the uninitiated</a>.</p>

<p><strong>There is no hash (#) symbol.</strong> Despite its huge popularity in programming, shell scripting, and even writing markdown. I found out later that you can type this symbol using <code>⌥3</code> (<code>Option+3</code>). Quite baffling.</p>

<p><strong>There is no delete key.</strong> This seemed like a terrible oversight at first, and six months later still seems a very questionable decision. However one quickly becomes proficient at using the arrow keys with the backspace to achieve the same effect. You can also use <code>⇧⌫</code> (<code>Shift+Backspace</code>) to exactly replicate the delete key. In Mac parlance, this is known as a &lsquo;forward delete&rsquo;.</p>

<h3><i class="icon-bolt"></i> The Battery</h3>

<p>Oh, the battery life is pretty huge, too. Six hours doing heavy dev work on a Windows VM, no problem. This is in stark contrast to my poor old Dell Precision, with its 1.5 hour battery-blastathon.</p>

<h2><a id="performance"></a> <i class="icon-forward"></i> The Performance</h2>

<p>I&rsquo;m only going to look at performance from an experiential point of view. There are
<a href="http://www.primatelabs.com/blog/2013/02/retina-macbook-pro-benchmarks/">benchmarks</a>
<a href="http://www.maclife.com/article/features/benchmarking_macbook_pro_retina_display">aplenty</a>
elsewhere, there&rsquo;s
<a href="http://www.apple.com/uk/macbook-pro/performance/">Apple&rsquo;s marketing spin on performance</a>
detailing choice components, and
<a href="http://www.notebookreview.com/default.asp?newsID=6495&amp;p=2">other</a>
<a href="http://www.everymac.com/systems/apple/macbook_pro/macbook-pro-retina-display-faq/macbook-pro-retina-display-early-2013-performance-benchmarks.html">numerate</a>
<a href="http://www.slashgear.com/retina-macbook-pro-benchmarks-show-minor-improvements-23270820/">articles</a>
on this topic. But for me, it&rsquo;s the experience that counts. And there&rsquo;s not much to say. It&rsquo;s fast. Really fast.</p>

<blockquote><p>There&rsquo;s not much to say. It&rsquo;s fast. Really fast.</p></blockquote>

<p>Since I&rsquo;m developing Microsoft.NET apps in Visual Studio, side-by-side with iOS Apps in XCode, I need to be able to switch seamlessly from one OS to the other. To that end, I run a Windows 8 virtual machine almost all the time that the Mac is switched on. Using Parallels Desktop, I devote half the resources (8GB RAM and 4 virtual CPUs, half the video memory), to the VM. There is <em>no noticable performance penalty at all on the Mac,</em> and the Windows VM runs very quickly. It&rsquo;s just a shade short of usual performance on dedicated hardware, but, and I&rsquo;m really fussy about performance, it is fast enough. My productivity is actually higher in this VM than on dedicated hardware&mdash;despite the minor performance loss&mdash;due to the <a href="#usability">sheer usability</a> of the rest of the machine.</p>

<h2><a id="usability"></a> <i class="icon-info-sign"></i> The Usability</h2>

<p>The MacBook Pro is the most usable computer I have ever interacted with. Its sheer usability has resulted in a number of changes to lifelong habits that I had never previously considered possible:</p>

<blockquote><p>Its sheer usability has resulted in a number of changes to lifelong habits.</p></blockquote>

<p><strong>I have stopped using an external mouse and keyboard entirely.</strong> The built-in trackpad is so good that I no longer have any need for a mouse at all. The keyboard is <em>good enough.</em> By using only the built-in keyboard&mdash;whether on the train or at my desk&mdash;my mucle memory has only one keyboard to remember, and thus touch-typing is much easier.</p>

<p><strong>I no longer <em>require</em> external monitors for reasonable productivity.</strong> This is, in fact, more related to the operating system. The brilliant implementation of multiple desktops in OS X Mountain Lion, and the ease of switching between them, means I no longer feel claustrophobic working on a single 15&ndash;inch display.</p>

<h2><a id="conclusion"></a> <i class="icon-thumbs-up"></i> The Conclusion</h2>

<p>The 15&ndash;inch MacBook Pro with Retina Display is <em>very</em> neat. It&rsquo;s also very thin for a desktop replacement. Easily light enough to work with on one&rsquo;s lap all day, and to carry to work and back daily without really noticing it. The battery life is huge, too, so you can work for a long time unplugged.</p>

<blockquote><p>The MacBook Pro with Retina Display is the most productive development workstation I have ever used.</p></blockquote>

<p>As a Microsoft.NET developer, the experience of working inside a Windows VM on a MacBook Pro is that of hugely increased efficiency, and even sanity, compared with working on any other hardware. OS X is a much more accomplished laptop OS than Windows, as I&rsquo;ll go into tomorrow.</p>

<p><strong>My recommendation: get one, or, better, get your work to get you one! The MacBook Pro with Retina Display is the most productive development workstation I have ever used.</strong></p>

<p><em>Disclaimer: I have written all this from memory, as I&rsquo;m currently in between Macs; thus the frequent use of past tense. Comments/trolls welcome ;)</em></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hello, blog.]]></title>
    <link href="http://blrgl.com/blog/2013/10/14/hello/"/>
    <updated>2013-10-14T16:26:00+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://blrgl.com/blog/2013/10/14/hello</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Over the past few years, I&rsquo;ve made copious notes on coding, software delivery, agile practices, and other <del>nerdy</del> exciting things. Most of these are locked up in private notes, in emails, or just rattling around my brain, and serving no useful purpose to anyone.</p>

<p>Now I find myself in the middle of a break in between jobs&mdash;a <em>very</em> rare two weeks off work, at home in London. I&rsquo;ve done all the household chores imaginable, I&rsquo;ve <a href="http://battlehack.org/london/">attended Battle Hack</a>, I&rsquo;ve been to visit family, I&rsquo;ve finally <a href="http://www.raspbmc.com/">set up RaspBMC</a> and <a href="http://en.alexnogard.com/install-openvpn-raspberry-pi-wheezy-debian/">installed OpenVPN on my Raspberry Pi</a>. I&rsquo;ve started to get involved with <a href="http://www.rapidftr.com/">RapidFTR</a> development. I&rsquo;ve been occasionally contributing to <a href="https://github.com/samsalisbury/modern-skins">some</a> <a href="https://github.com/samsalisbury/righteous-git-hooks">projects</a> on GitHub. I still have a lot of free time. I can&rsquo;t put it off any longer. Welcome, world, to some extra <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Information_pollution">informational pollution</a>, and maybe the odd interesting thing. Courtesy of <a href="https://twitter.com/samsalisbury">yours</a> <a href="http://uk.linkedin.com/in/samsalisbury/">truly</a>.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
